

BANGAH M'BAYI YANN

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

bino26.github.io

(225) 07 48 32 78 82

yannmarierene@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/yannbangah-bino/

PROFILE

I'm a bilingual web developer with an expertise in front-end and back-end development. I design and develop web applications using the latest technologies to deliver the product with quality code. I'm available for a possible interview.

SKILLS

- Web Development: Javascript, Node JS, Express JS, PHP, C#, Python, HTML, CSS, SCSS, TypeScript, JAVA, ASP.NET, REACT JS.
- Databases: MYSQL, SQL SERVER, MongoDB, Firebase
- API Rest Development
- Versionning Tools: GIT, GITLAB, GITHUB
- Project Management Tools: Trello, Airtable, Notion

WORK EXPERIENCE

Back-end Developer Intern

CodeTheDream • USA, Remote

Oct. 2023 - Jan. 2024

Main missions:

- Creation of a quiz application for the elimination entrance test at Code The Dream with functions such as user registration, user role (user,admin),answers and many other components.
 Adding a note sheet to allow users to note answers and also concepts that are important to them.
- · User connection and cookies verification using the Jsonwebtoken .
- Establishment of an administrator system to monitor the journey and support of each learner.

Web Developer Intern

June. 2023 - Oct 2023

Digital Bhem • Inde, Remote

Main missions:

• Design a voting system for the election of the president of a university with Laravel .

Web Developer Intern

May. 2023 - June 2023

GlobalTech Pvt • Inde, Remote

Main missions:

 Creation of responsive, accessible and dynamic web pages to allow user to easily navigate on the website.

Web Developer Intern

Apr. 2023 - May 2023

LetsGrowMore • Inde, Remote

Main missions:

- · Fixed bugs on existing web applications.
- Interact with user data using an REST API

FullStack Developer Intern

Bharat Intern • Inde , Remote

Mar. 2023- Apr2023

- · Web Application Development
- · Creation of a content management tool

EDUCATION

Back-end Development

may. 2023- oct. 2023

Code The Dream • USA

Software Engineering

febr. 2022 - apr. 2023

ALX AFRICA -HOLBERTON SCHOOL • Nairobi, Kenya

Bachelor in Computer Science (BCS)

nov. 2019 - apr. 2023

Université Internationale de Cote d'Ivoire • Abidjan, Côte d'Ivoire

BACCALAURÉAT D july. 2019

Collège Adventiste Abidjan • Abidjan, Côte d'Ivoire

LANGUAGES

French

CERTIFICATIONS

- Certificate of Completion Software Engineering
 ALX AFRICA/HOLBERTON SCHOOL
- Introduction to Cybersecurity

Cisco Networking Academy

Get Connected from Cisco Networking Academy

Cisco Networking Academy

Certificate of Completion Full Stack Development(Node.js, Express)
 Code The Dream

CENTER OF INTERETS

- Artificial Intelligence
- Cybersecurity
- Tennis
- Volunteering



BANGAH M'BAYI YANN

FULLSTACK DEVELOPPEUR

bino26.github.io

(225) 07 48 32 78 82

yannmarierene@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/yannbangah-bino/

A PROPOS DE MOI

Je suis un développeur web bilingue ayant une expertise dans le développement front-end et back-end. Je conçois et développe des applications Web en utilisant les dernières technologues pour livrer le produit avec un code de qualité. Je reste à votre disposition pour un éventuel entretien.

COMPÉTENCES

- Développement Web: Javascript, Node JS, Express JS, PHP, C#, Python, HTML, CSS, SCSS, TypeScript, JAVA, ASP.NET, REACT JS.
- Base de données : MYSQL, SQL SERVER, MongoDB, Firebase
- Developpement d'API Rest
- Outils de versionning : GIT, GITLAB ,GITHUB
- Outils de gestion de projet : Trello, Airtable, Notion

EXPÉRIENCE DE TRAVAIL

Back-end Developer Intern

CodeTheDream • USA, Remote

Oct. 2023 - Jan. 2024

Principales missions:

- Création d'une application de quiz pour le test d'entrée éliminatoire à Code The Dream avec les fonctions tels que l'enregistrement de l'utilisateur, le rôle de l'utilisateur (user, admin), les réponses et bien d'autres composantes. L'ajout d'une feuille de note pour permettre aux utilisateurs de noter les réponses et aussi des notions qui leurs sont importantes.
- La connexion des utilisateurs et la vérification des cookies grâce au Jsonwebtoken.
- Mise en place d'un système administrateur pour suivre le parcours et l'accompagnement de chaque apprenant

Web Developer Intern

Juin. 2023 - Oct 2023

Digital Bhem • Inde, Remote

Principales missions:

Conception d'un système de vote pour l'élection du président d'une université avec Laravel.

Web Developer Intern

Mai. 2023 - Juin 2023

GlobalTech Pvt • Inde, Remote

Principales missions:

 Création de pages web réactives, accessibles et dynamiques pour permettre aux utilisateurs de naviguer facilement sur le site.

Web Developer Intern

Avr. 2023 - Mai 2023

Mar. 2023- Avr 2023

LetsGrowMore • Inde, Remote

Principales missions:

- Correction de bugs sur des applications et sites web existants.
- Interagir avec les données de l'utilisateur grâce à une REST API

FullStack Developer Intern

Bharat Intern • Inde , Remote

e , Remote

- Développement d'application web
- Création d'Outil de gestion de contenu

FORMATIONS

Back-end Development

mai. 2023- oct. 2023

Code The Dream • USA

Software Engineering

fev. 2022 - avr. 2023

ALX AFRICA -HOLBERTON SCHOOL • Nairobi, Kenya

Licence en Informatique et Sciences du Numérique (ISN)

nov. 2019 - avr. 2023

Université Internationale de Cote d'Ivoire • Abidjan, Côte d'Ivoire

BACCALAURÉAT D juil. 2019

Collège Adventiste Abidjan • Abidjan, Côte d'Ivoire

LANGUES

Français Anglais

CERTIFICATIONS

- Certificate of Completion Software Engineering ALX AFRICA/HOLBERTON SCHOOL
- Introduction à la Cybersecurite
 Cisco Networking Academy
- Get Connected de Cisco Networking Academy
 Cisco Networking Academy
- Certificate of Completion Full Stack Development(Node.js ,Express)
 Code The Dream

CENTRE D'INTERETS

- Intelligence Artificielle
- Cybersecurite
- Tennis
- Benevolat